clesty.com 2015-02-07

# Privacy Policy

Clesty takes your privacy seriously. This privacy policy describes what personal information we collect and how we use it. See this privacy policy primer to learn more about privacy policies in general.

**Routine Information Collection**

All web servers track basic information about their visitors. This information includes, but is not limited to, IP addresses, browser details, timestamps and referring pages. None of this information can personally identify specific visitors to this site. The information is tracked for routine administration and maintenance purposes.

Advertising partners and other third parties may also use cookies, scripts and/or web beacons to track visitors to our site in order to display advertisements and other useful information. Such tracking is done directly by the third parties through their own servers and is subject to their own privacy policies.

**INFORMATION SUBMITTED BY YOU**

_Zip Code and Email Address_ : On some of the Websites, you have the choice of providing your ZIP Code or email address if, for example, you would like to receive local services or information from us.

_Account or Profile Information_ : On some of the Websites, you may be able to become a registered user and create your user profile. When you decide to become a registered user, we ask for some basic contact information, such as a username and your ZIP Code and email address. If you purchase products through a Nextag Store (described below), you may enter additional account information. You also may choose to provide other information about yourself, either as part of your public profile or otherwise, such as your age, gender or interests. We may use the information that we collect or receive to create a user profile in connection with your account. A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users that detail their viewing preferences, activities and interactions.

_Cookies and Web Beacons_ :Where necessary, Clesty uses cookies to store information about a visitor’s preferences and history in order to better serve the visitor and/or present the visitor with customized content.

Controlling Your Privacy Note that you can change your browser settings to disable cookies if you have privacy concerns. Disabling cookies for all sites is not recommended as it may interfere with your use of some sites. The best option is to disable or enable cookies on a per-site basis. Consult your browser documentation for instructions on how to block cookies and other tracking mechanisms. This list of web browser privacy management links may also be useful.

**Special Note About Our Advertising Partner**

Any advertisements served by Our Advertising Partner, and affiliated companies may be controlled using cookies. These cookies allow Our Partner to display ads based on your visits to this site and other sites that use advertising services.

**PEOPLE UNDER 18 YEARS OLD**

Our Websites are not intended for use by people under eighteen (18) years of age. If you are under 18, please do not send any information to us. By accessing Websites or using our services, you represent that you are 18 years of age or older.

**Contact Information**

Concerns or questions about this privacy policy can be directed to here for further clarification.
